[{"question": "Wahlsystem", "answer": "electoral system", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Rede", "answer": "speech", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Politik", "answer": "politics", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Mehrheit", "answer": "majority", "times_correct": 3},
{"question": "Debatte", "answer": "debate", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Botschaft", "answer": "embassy", "times_correct": 2},
{"question": "Abstellkammer", "answer": "closet ", "times_correct": 135},
{"question": "Bad", "answer": "bathroom", "times_correct": 50},
{"question": "Balkon", "answer": "balcony", "times_correct": 66},
{"question": "Bauernhof", "answer": "farm", "times_correct": 63},
{"question": "Fenster", "answer": "window", "times_correct": 22},
{"question": "Dach", "answer": "roof", "times_correct": 5},
{"question": "Keller", "answer": "cellar", "times_correct": 2},
{"question": "Mauer", "answer": "wall", "times_correct": 3},
{"question": "Schafzimmer", "answer": "bedroom", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Tor", "answer": "gate", "times_correct": 3},
{"question": "Wohnung", "answer": "flat", "times_correct": 2},
{"question": "Beruf (im Handwerk)", "answer": "trade", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Beruf (meistens mit Studium)", "answer": "profession", "times_correct": 2},
{"question": "Beruf allgemein", "answer": "job", "times_correct": 2},
{"question": "Vollzeit", "answer": "a full-time job", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Lohn", "answer": "wages", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Lebenslauf", "answer": "CV", "times_correct": 1},
{"question": "Bewerbung", "answer": "application", "times_correct": 2},
{"question": "Fortschritt", "answer": "progress", "times_correct": 3}]